<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethical Hacking on NOTES of Ethical Hacking Student</title>
    <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/categories/ethical-hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethical Hacking on NOTES of Ethical Hacking Student</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:52:53 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://notes.ashishghimire.com/categories/ethical-hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installing VMware and Vulnhub Kioptrix</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/installingkioptrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:52:53 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/installingkioptrix/</guid>
      <description>So our Journey of Hack starts here. We are going to install VMware to run our Vulnerable Machine Kioptrix.
Download VMware or Virtual Box Download Kioptrix a ready made Vulnerable Machine provided by TCM-SEC from Vulnhub Now Import downloaded VM Image on your virtual engine. - Open - Default Username: john - Default password: TwoCows2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnaissance Part 2</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/reconaissancepart2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 22:38:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/reconaissancepart2/</guid>
      <description>OSINT Open Source Intelligence Email OSINT Email Discovery hunter.io phonebook.cz voilanorbert.com Clearbit - Chromium Plugin tools.verifyemailaddress.io (Verify Email Address) Use Forgot Password to tie email accounts.
In this way a recovery email can be tied to another email address.
Password OSINT Credentials Stuffing Automate Prevoiusly found username &amp;amp; Passwords Dehashed Hunting Breached Credentials with DeHashed Find Subdomains *.domain.com Sublist3r python3 sublist3r.py -d domain.com Owasp Tomnomnom Build and Frameworks Know how website is built builtwith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconnaissance Part 1</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/reconnaissancepart1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 22:01:58 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/reconnaissancepart1/</guid>
      <description>Passive Reconnaissance Physical Location Satellite Images Drone Recon Building Layouts, etc. Social Job Information Employees Name, Job, Title, Manager Name Picture Badge Picture Desk Photos Computer Photos Web/Host Target Validation Whois nslookup dnsrecon Finding Subdomains Google Fu dig nmap sublist3r bluto crt.sh Fingerprinting Finding what is used on the app. nmap wappalyzer WhatWeb BuiltWith Wetcat Data Breaches haveibeenpwned Breach-Parse weleakinfo </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ethical Hacker Methodology </title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/day1-hacking-methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/day1-hacking-methodology/</guid>
      <description>Reconissance Info Gathering. Active
Scanning and Enumeration Using Different Tools Finding Open Ports and Vulneribilities Passive
Google Search Social Media Scan Facebook Twitter Linkedin, etc. Scanning &amp;amp; Enumeration Scanning Through PC Nmap Nessus Nikto, etc.7 Gaining Access Exploitation Maintaining Access Also Scanning And Enumeration Covering Tracks Deleting Logs and Cleaning Up The Method is also called 5 Stages of Ethical Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
