<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Free Hosting on NOTES</title>
    <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/tags/free-hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Free Hosting on NOTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:43:19 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://notes.ashishghimire.com/tags/free-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Github</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/githubinstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:43:19 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/githubinstall/</guid>
      <description>Windows Install simply download Git EXE file from Git for Windows Run it and Install Check version from command prompt with git version Linux - Debian/Ubuntu/Kali Usually it comes pre installed. If its not in your system open Terminal and use the code:
Update your repository with sudo apt-get update Install sudo apt-get install git-all After install check version git version Mac Go to macOS Git Installer After installation open terminal and use code to check installation git version For more info on installation visit this Github Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Host Hugo Sites On GITHUB</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/hugotogithub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 23:35:24 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/hugotogithub/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is free, static, fast and minimal website creator. In this blog we are going to setup this current Hugo site (without modification) and deploy to Github Pages for free. I am also going to setup so new posts can be added and published on your website everytime.
Login Github Install Hugo On System Create Two Repos on Github a. blog Houses our hugo code b. username.github.io For website generated pages Get Theme for Hugo (PaperMod) Clone &amp;lsquo;blog &amp;rsquo; Repo in Desktop (notesite) git clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Push</title>
      <link>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/testing-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 23:35:24 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.ashishghimire.com/posts/testing-push/</guid>
      <description>Lets see if i have to push</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
